talkgold.com 2019-06-25

# Privacy Policy

If you plan to use Talkgold.com and access the content it provides, you must pay closer attention to this particular section. Once you have visited our website and started using the services we provide, you automatically agree with all Privacy terms described in the text below. So, make sure you clearly understand the info below in reference to Talkgold.com that reserves the right to collect and store users’ data. We guarantee to use users’ data for purposes that do not contradict with this section. Please, note, you are not supposed to opt for Talkgold.com services or access any of its sections in case you disagree with any of the following Privacy Policy statements.

The points you will see were conducted in regards to all possible types of users’ data we can generate and store. They may include software and hardware info, digital tools, and other data that will help our website to deliver an enhanced customer service out of the box. Pay attention that the given section applies not only to Talkgold.com but also to any of its partners or subsidiaries in the face of affiliates.

Do not hesitate to contact our support representatives every time you need to resolve the ay issue connected with Privacy Terms. You can ask any question and always count on ASAP assistance. Users should clearly understand that Talkgold.com is the only side to proceed with any changes, corrections or amendments of the given section without giving users a notice. So, make sure you currently revise the info in this section to keep in touch with the latest updates.

Type of Users’ Data Collected by Talkgold.com

The main mission is to establish a comprehensive approach to ensure 100% of users’ satisfaction while using our website. For this reason, we may require some users’ info in order to improve and boost our service delivery. The website can collect the following:

  1.  **Users’ Personal Info**. It may include his or her name, email address, personal social page links, phone numbers or surname. In other words, users’ personal data means all necessary info you need to indicate when completing the registration process.

  2.  **Affiliates Info**. We want our users to be aware of all our partners and affiliates who can act as our subsidiaries. At the same time, we reserve the right to generate personal data from third parties that have established a partnership with Talkgold.com. The data may include the above-mentioned details in addition to photos, social accounts, etc.

Users’ Contact Information

Talkgold.com has the right to generate your contact info not just for getting in touch when resolving technical or other issues but also to forward newsletters or personalized offers. Users may receive different types of notifications:

  1. Promotional materials and personalized offers. Our mission is to ensure 100% unique and flexible online shopping experience. For this reason, we establish an individual approach to our every user. We thoroughly pick the best offers on the market and send them to users that are likely to be interested. The info can be shared with the company’s affiliates and partners.

  2. Additional data. Here at Talkgold.com, we do our best to ensure the best and fastest content delivery. For this reason, we might need to generate additional data such as IP address, IDFA identifiers, Google Ads IDS, device location, cookies, and more. Also, note that we can browse technical characteristic and specs of the device you use in addition to carrier, OS or other details.

Cookies

Talkgold.com uses cookies to generate and keep the collected data as prescribed by the given section. The website may collect all types of cookies including persistent and temporary. The main reason for collecting cookies is to establish a faster content transfer and connection between the website and the end user. You are free to remove persistent cookies from your PC or any other device whenever needed. You can do it manually using the settings in your browser.

Our users should keep in mind that Talkgold.com never interacts with the given policy and never uses cookies to do any harm or identify our website users from other people who visit Talkgold.com. None of the action considers having digital or privacy threats. Users are free to use browser settings to stop sending cookies as well as block them. However, it may lead to limited website access with some of its essential services blocked. Make sure you are always aware of your cookies disabled or enabled. Set your browser to send notifications in case of blocked or enabled cookies.

Subsidiary Website Links

When visiting Talkgold.com, users can come across links that may take them to third-party websites. They mainly include the company’s subsidiaries, affiliates or partners. The reason for providing links to them is to boost customers’ service as well as deliver the most actual and up-to-date info generated from reviews, testimonials, overlooks, etc. At the same time, we are not responsible for actions made by third parties that violate the given terms as well as their own Privacy Policy. Once you have used the link and got to a third-party website, you automatically agree with its terms of service and policy.

Users’ Age Limit

Our website can be accessed by users who are over 14. Otherwise, proper parental control must be established. Make sure you are able to prove parental consent in case your children under 14 will try to access our website service. If not, we will not be able to help you when resolving issues related to this type of violation. Do not hesitate to contact our support team and check if your kids under 14 try to use any of our website services. You will get full info to prevent possible problems in the future.

Sharing Users’ Info

Do we share users’ data with third parties? Yes, we do. Talkgold.com reserves the right to provide users’ info to any of its partners, affiliates or subsidiaries if we are sure it will help to enhance our services and deliver personalized offers our users will appreciate. Talkgold.com has the right to provide users; info to third parties under the following conditions:

  * As indicated in the given privacy terms.

  * In case of any actions taking place such as rebranding, acquiring, relocation, reorganization, etc.

  * In case state law representatives require users’ personal data to prevent any kinds of illegal actions or crimes.

Do not use Talkgold.com services and content in case you disagree with any of the above-mentioned.

Data Security Means

Talkgold.com established an accurate and thorough approach when it comes to data security. We implement different technological means that meet the highest digital safety standards. They have proved to work well when it comes to scanning, detecting or eliminating different types of frauds, hacker attacks and other online threats that can harm users’ personal data or result in the info leaking.

How We Access, Process and Update Users’ Data

Talkgold.com deals with all types of users’ data described in this section. The website uses different tools to access and process users’ info. Moreover, the website administration monitors users’ data to come up with on-time updates if necessary. The main mission is to retain maximum accuracy and precision. It is also necessary for enhanced service and personalized offers. Talkgold.com reserves the right to update the info, add new details or delete some pieces of information that are out-of-date or of no use for the website.

Users can initiate data processing or update. All you need is to keep in touch with the Talkgold.com administration and provide new details as well as ask to remove old ones. We guarantee that your out-of-date info will be removed instantly. The procedure is 100% free. You will not be charged for the data updates or disclosure although the website can charge extra fees for some specific actions. Keep I mind that you are not allowed to access info and personal details related to third-party users.

Assistance and Customer Support

Our mission is to establish beneficiary relations with each and every user. Your feedback is also very important for us when it comes to improving our services. For this reason, we offer several ways to keep in touch with the website representatives, administration or support team.

You can find all the available contact methods in a special contact section. We constantly team up with different organizations and official institutions to ensure maximum data privacy in addition to risk-free digital service.

Privacy Policy Corrections and Updates

Talkgold.com is the only force to make all necessary corrections, changes, amendments or updates of the given section. Moreover, the website administration is not obliged to notify users regarding the changes that have been made. Users agree to check the given terms regularly in order to keep in touch with all the latest updates.

Keep in mind that you automatically agree with all changes and corrections made in case you continue using our services. Avoid accessing the website as well as its content in case you disagree with changes and updates made to this particular section.

Additional Statements

Every user who signs or logs in agrees that Talkgold.com will collect, process, keep or update his or her personal data. The website is permitted to share that data with third parties in the face of company’s affiliates, partners or subsidiaries located both inside the country and abroad. The right to use personal data outside the country is prescribed by the given privacy terms. Do not use our service if you do not agree with any of the statement.

Talkgold.com can transfer personal data to another country and use it in the same way there as described in this section. At the same time, Talkgold.com guarantees that it will never harm users’ info or never result in digital threats, hacker attacks of frauds. The company agrees to provide the same security level despite the data location.

Keep in Touch with Talkgold.com Administration

As it was mentioned before, users are free to ask any question or keep in touch to resolve different issues with our website representatives. They will provide professional assistance in case you need to provide updated personal info or disclose the existing one.
